Let's take our extra hips, add them to our Egyptian walk and then travel with them, forward and back.
So let's start with our basic so we're going to step on the right foot.
Left hip goes up and drop.
Step up drop.
Good.
Now remember as we travel, you want to make sure you keep your feet together.
So it's step together, lift drop. Step together, lift drop. Step together, lift drop. Step together, lift drop. Backwards, same thing.
Step now remember your actually the up the down and the out. Up down out. Up down step. Up down step.
Good. Up down step. Up down step. Up down step. Try it a little faster and step. Up down. One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
You can travel forward and back.
Good so practice going back and forth.
Good.
Keep the feet together.
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three.
Good.